{
    "subject": "resource/Frederick_M._Ausubel",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableStudent",
    "object": "resource/Joanne_Chory",
    "human_readable": "Frederick M. Ausubel was notable for being a student of Joanne Chory.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9591256380081177,
            "question": "Who was Frederick M. Ausubel a student of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.91916424036026,
            "question": "Was Frederick M. Ausubel a teacher or a student?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9072237610816956,
            "question": "What field of study might Frederick M. Ausubel have been involved in based on his relationship with Joanne Chory?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8537694215774536,
            "question": "What is the significance of a student-teacher relationship like the one between Frederick M. Ausubel and Joanne Chory?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7957577705383301,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the relationship between Frederick M. Ausubel and Joanne Chory?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7554288506507874,
            "question": "Are there any other notable students of Joanne Chory?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5647260546684265,
            "question": "What is Joanne Chory known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5431729555130005,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Frederick M. Ausubel's work or accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26161399483680725,
            "question": "Can you provide more details about Joanne Chory's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04537089914083481,
            "question": "What are some key aspects of the relationship between a mentor and their student?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Frederick M. Ausubel was notable for being a student of Joanne Chory.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7866_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide more details about Joanne Chory's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7866_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Frederick M. Ausubel's work or accomplishments?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7866_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Joanne Chory known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7866_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7866_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7866_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7866_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7866_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7866_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7866_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7866_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7866_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7866_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7866_37.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not mention Frederick M. Ausubel being a student of Joanne Chory. Instead, it is stated that Joanne Chory joined the Fred Ausubel laboratory for her postdoctoral studies to work on signal transduction in plants."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Joanne Chory was a student in Fred Ausubel's laboratory during her postdoctoral studies, not the other way around.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text describes Joanne Chory as a student in Fred Ausubel's lab during her postdoctoral studies.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Joanne Chory was a postdoctoral student in Fred Ausubel's laboratory, not the other way around.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Joanne Chory was a student of Frederick M. Ausubel in his laboratory at Harvard Medical School for her postdoctoral studies, not the other way around.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}